So we can run yarn Hardhead compile.
现在我们运行 "yarn hardhat compile"
And you'll see we actually get an error here.
你会看到我们遇到了报错
Library at chain link slash contracts imported from contracts slash fund me dot soul is not installed,
“库 "@chainlink/contracts" 导入自 "contracts/FundMe.sol"，并没有安装”
try installing it using npm.
“请尝试使用 npm 进行安装”
In remix, we went ahead and just imported at chainlink slash contracts, right from our NPM and or GitHub.
在 Remix 中我们只需要从 npm 或 GitHub 中直接导入 "@chainlink/contracts"
But in our local code,
但在我们的本地代码中，
we have to tell Hardhead specifically, where to get this from,
我们还必须具体告诉 Hardhat 从哪里获取这个东西
we want to download this specifically from the NPM package manager at chainlink slash contracts,
具体来说，我们要从 npm 包管理器上下载这个 "@chainlink/contracts"
we can download it simply by running yarn, add dash dash dev at chainlink slash contracts.
我们可以简单地使用 "yarn add --dev @chainlink/contracts" 来把它下载下来
Now that we've downloaded it into our file,
现在我们已经把它下载到我们的文件里了
we'll be able to see it in Node modules here.
我们可以在 "node_modules" 这里看到它
Hardhead is now smart enough to know that at chain link slash contracts
Hardhat 十分智能，它知道这里的 "@chainlink/contracts"
is going to point to that node module that we have.
指的就是 "node_modules" 中安装的那个
So we can now run yarn Hardhead compile
所以现在我们就可以运行 "yarn hardhat compile"
boom, now we can see compiled three solidity files successfully.
嘭！现在我们可以看到“已成功编译 3 个 Solidity 文件